<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>All Bills</title>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/</link>
<description>
A list of up to 50 of most recent bills for the current session
</description>
<copyright>Copyright 2026, Houses of Parliament</copyright>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:53:10 Z</lastBuildDate>
<a10:id>https://bills-api.parliament.uk/Rss/AllBill</a10:id>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3879</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3879</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Tobacco and Vapes Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the supply of tobacco, vapes and other products, including provision prohibiting the sale of tobacco to people born on or after 1 January 2009 and provision about the licensing of retail sales and the registration of retailers; to enable product and information requirements to be imposed in connection with tobacco, vapes and other products; to control the advertising and promotion of tobacco, vapes and other products; and to make provision about smoke-free places, vape-free places and heated tobacco-free places.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T18:40:28Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3938</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3938</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Crime and Policing Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about anti-social behaviour, offensive weapons, offences against people (including sexual offences), property offences, the criminal exploitation of persons, sex offenders, stalking and public order; to make provision about powers of the police, the border force and other similar persons; to make provision about confiscation; to make provision about the police; to make provision about terrorism and national security, and about international agreements relating to crime; to make provision about the criminal liability of bodies; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T18:07:20Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4046</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4046</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
National Insurance Contributions (Employer Pensions Contributions) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision to amend section 4 of the Social Security Contributions and Benefits Act 1992, and section 4 of the Social Security Contributions and Benefits (Northern Ireland) Act 1992, so that amounts of salary sacrificed for employer pensions contributions pursuant to optional remuneration arrangements are liable to national insurance contributions.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T17:33:05Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee of the whole House">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4059</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4059</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Universal Credit (Removal of Two Child Limit) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision to remove the two child limit on the child element of universal credit.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T17:15:54Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee of the whole House">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4034</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4034</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Industry and Exports (Financial Assistance) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Amend section 8(5) of the Industrial Development Act 1982 and section 6 of the Export and Investment Guarantees Act 1991.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T16:52:46Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4062</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4062</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Medical Training (Prioritisation) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision about the prioritisation of graduates from medical schools in the United Kingdom and certain other persons for places on medical training programmes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-20T16:49:13Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3946</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3946</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Planning and Infrastructure Act 2025</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about infrastructure; to make provision about town and country planning; to make provision for a scheme, administered by Natural England, for a nature restoration levy payable by developers; to make provision about development corporations; to make provision about the compulsory purchase of land; to make provision about environmental outcomes reports; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-19T17:11:09Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee of the whole House">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4022</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4022</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Northern Ireland Troubles Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make new provision to address the legacy of the Northern Ireland Troubles.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-19T16:59:11Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4002</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4002</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>English Devolution and Community Empowerment Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about combined authorities, combined county authorities, the Greater London Authority, local councils, police and crime commissioners and fire and rescue authorities, local audit and terms in business tenancies about rent.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-19T16:38:37Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3982</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3982</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Pension Schemes Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about pension schemes; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-19T16:37:29Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3774</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3774</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Ballot Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Terminally Ill Adults (End of Life) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to allow adults who are terminally ill, subject to safeguards and protections, to request and be provided with assistance to end their own life; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-19T14:55:16Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4030</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4030</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Railways Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about railways and railway services; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-18T18:11:58Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3968</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3968</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Victims and Courts Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision about the experience of victims within the criminal justice system; about the functions of the Commissioner for Victims and Witnesses; and about procedure and the administration of criminal justice.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-17T16:42:58Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3897</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3897</link>
<category>Private Bill</category>
<category>Lords</category>
<title>Malvern Hills Bill [HL]</title>
<description>
A Bill to repeal and re-enact certain enactments relating to the Malvern Hills Conservators and the management of the Malvern Hills, to reconstitute and rename those Conservators as the Malvern Hills Trust and to confer further powers on the Malvern Hills Trust, to make further provision in relation to the Malvern Hills, and for other purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-17T11:58:51Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3381</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3381</link>
<category>Private Bill</category>
<category>Lords</category>
<title>Royal Albert Hall Bill [HL]</title>
<description>
A Bill to amend certain provisions of the Royal Albert Hall Act 1966 relating to the annual contribution payable by the Members of the Corporation towards the general purposes of the Royal Albert Hall; to make further provision regarding the exclusion of the Members from the hall.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-16T16:22:23Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4016</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4016</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Biodiversity Beyond National Jurisdiction Act 2026</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision for and in connection with the implementation by the United Kingdom of the Agreement under the United Nations Convention on the Law of the Sea on the Conservation and Sustainable Use of Marine Biological Diversity of Areas Beyond National Jurisdiction.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-16T11:00:37Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3810</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3810</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Secure 16 to 19 Academies Act 2026</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the notice period for termination of funding agreements for secure 16 to 19 Academies; to make provision about the Secretary of State’s duty to consider the impact on existing educational institutions when it is proposed to establish or expand a secure 16 to 19 Academy; and to alter the consultation question required when it is proposed to establish or expand a secure 16 to 19 Academy.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-16T10:58:54Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3783</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3783</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Ballot Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Licensing Hours Extensions Act 2026</title>
<description>
A Bill to amend the Licensing Act 2003 so that licensing hours Orders can be made by negative resolution statutory instrument.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-16T10:56:59Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4080</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4080</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Representation of the People Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision extending the right to vote to 16 and 17 year olds; to make provision about the registration of voters; to make provision about the administration and conduct of elections, referendums and recall petitions; to make provision about election agents’ addresses; to make provision about political expenditure and political donations; to make provision about information to be included in electronic campaigning material; to make provision about offences and civil sanctions in connection with elections, referendums and recall petitions and with donations and expenditure for political purposes; to make provision about the disclosure of information by the Electoral Commission; to make provision about the disqualification of offenders for holding elective offices, and their sentencing, where offences are aggravated by hostility towards persons involved in elections, referendums or recall petitions or holders of such offices; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-13T13:14:52Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4035</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4035</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Cyber Security and Resilience (Network and Information Systems) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision, including provision amending the Network and Information Systems Regulations 2018, about the security and resilience of network and information systems used or relied on in connection with the carrying on of essential activities.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-13T10:46:22Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4042</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4042</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Finance (No. 2) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision in connection with finance.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-12T17:35:11Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Consideration of Lords amendments">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3909</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3909</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Children’s Wellbeing and Schools Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the safeguarding and welfare of children; about support for children in care or leaving care; about regulation of care workers; about regulation of establishments and agencies under Part 2 of the Care Standards Act 2000; about employment of children; about breakfast club provision and school uniform; about attendance of children at school; about regulation of independent educational institutions; about inspections of schools and colleges; about teacher misconduct; about Academies and teachers at Academies; repealing section 128 of the Education Act 2002; about school places and admissions; about establishing new schools; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-12T16:54:27Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3998</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3998</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Clean Air (Human Rights) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to establish the right to breathe clean air; to require the Secretary of State to achieve and maintain clean air in England; to make provision about environmental targets and minimum standards in relation to clean air; to make provision about the powers, duties and functions of public bodies in England in relation to air pollution; to give the Office for Environmental Protection additional powers and duties related to clean air; to require the Secretary of State to comply with the United Nations Convention on Long-Range Transboundary Air Pollution; to require the Secretary of State and public authorities to apply specified environmental principles in carrying out their duties under this Act; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-12T12:44:19Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4081</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4081</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Short-term Let Accommodation (Data Sharing Requirements) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to require certain persons or organisations to share specified data relating to the short-term letting of accommodation with regulatory authorities; to amend the Data Protection Act 2018 in connection with that requirement; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-12T10:04:24Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="3rd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3779</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3779</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Ballot Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Rare Cancers Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision to incentivise research and investment into the treatment of rare types of cancer; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-12T09:35:58Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Report stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4019</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4019</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Public Office (Accountability) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Impose a duty on public authorities and public officials to act with candour, transparency and frankness; to make provision for the enforcement of that duty in their dealings with inquiries and investigations; to require public authorities to promote and take steps to maintain ethical conduct within all parts of the authority; to create an offence in relation to public authorities and public officials who mislead the public; to create further offences in relation to the misconduct of persons who hold public office and to abolish the common law offence of misconduct in public office; to make provision enabling persons to participate at inquiries and investigations where the conduct of public authorities may be in issue; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T21:26:18Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3850</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3850</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Vaccine Damage Payments Act (Review) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to place a duty on the Secretary of State to review, and publish a report on, the merits of increasing the relevant statutory sum under the Vaccine Damage Payments Act 1979 for all claims since 1 January 2020 by an amount representing the amount of inflation since 2007.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T14:37:44Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3856</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3856</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Exemption from Value Added Tax (Miscellaneous Provisions) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to exempt from Value Added Tax goods or services which are beneficial to the environment, to health and safety, to education or for charitable purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T14:36:33Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4021</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4021</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Child Poverty Strategy (Removal of Two Child Limit) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to require the Secretary of State to publish a child poverty strategy which includes proposals for removing the limit on the number of children or qualifying young persons included in the calculation of an award of Universal Credit; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T14:35:09Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3868</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3868</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Illegal Immigration (Offences) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to create offences in respect of persons who have entered the UK illegally or who have remained in the UK without legal authority; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T14:29:12Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3847</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3847</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Exemption from Value Added Tax (Listed Places of Worship) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to exempt from Value Added Tax repairs to listed places of worship; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T14:24:52Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4079</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4079</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Eating Disorders (Training) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to establish a requirement for persons providing certain public services to undertake training relating to eating disorders and disordered eating; to make provision about the delivery and content of such training; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T11:59:57Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="3rd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3972</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3972</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Sustainable Aviation Fuel Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to Make provision about sustainable aviation fuel.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T11:47:54Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4078</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4078</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Images (Non-consensual Recording and Distribution) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to create offences relating to the non-consensual recording of images of a person and the online distribution of such images for profit with the purpose of obtaining sexual gratification or of causing humiliation or distress to that person; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-11T11:47:06Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4044</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4044</link>
<category>Private Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Cheltenham Borough Council (Markets) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision for the repeal of section 83 of the Cheltenham Improvement Act 1852; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-09T10:48:16Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4077</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4077</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Human Remains (Prohibition of Sale, Purchase and Advertising) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to prohibit giving or receiving a reward for the supply of, or for offering to supply, human remains or any object partially consisting of human remains; to prohibit advertising the sale, exchange, or offer of sale or exchange, of human remains or any object partially consisting of human remains; to make provision for specified exemptions from those prohibitions; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-05T09:39:00Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4076</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4076</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>British-Made Bricks (Proposals) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to require the Secretary of State to publish proposals for measures to increase the use of British-made bricks in construction projects in the United Kingdom, including specific measures relating to the building of new homes; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-04T13:52:34Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3863</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3863</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
British Broadcasting Corporation (Privatisation) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision for the privatisation of the British Broadcasting Corporation; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-04T13:39:53Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3843</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3843</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Meat (Information About Method of Killing) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to require producers, suppliers and retailers of meat to indicate clearly whether the animal has been killed in accordance with religious rites without prior stunning; to require the Secretary of State to collect and publish specified information relating to meat slaughtered in accordance with such practice; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-04T13:38:56Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3835</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3835</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Building Regulations (Minimum Standards) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to set minimum standards for the building of new homes in relation to quality and energy efficiency; to place requirements on developers of new homes; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-03T10:06:11Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3937</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3937</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Political Donations Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about a cap on political donations; to make provision for a review to recommend the level at which such a cap should be set and to consider the impact of such a cap; to make provision about political donations made by foreign nationals through companies; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-03T10:04:48Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4058</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4058</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Property (Registration and Valuation) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about requirements relating to the registration and valuation of domestic and non-domestic property; to make provision about exemptions from such requirements; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-03T10:02:15Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Committee stage">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3094</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3094</link>
<category>Hybrid Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>High Speed Rail (Crewe - Manchester) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision for a railway between a junction with Phase 2a of High Speed 2 south of Crewe in Cheshire and Manchester Piccadilly Station; for a railway between Hoo Green in Cheshire and a junction with the West Coast Main Line at Bamfurlong, south of Wigan; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-02-03T09:59:00Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4047</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4047</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Fireworks (Noise Control etc) Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the maximum noise levels of fireworks which may be sold to the public; to require that specified information about noise levels is included on labelling and in sales information for fireworks; to require the Secretary of State to review the impact of firework noise on the welfare of veterans, neurodivergent people, people with certain medical conditions, and animals; to provide local authorities with power to regulate the use of fireworks in certain circumstances, and to enforce such regulation; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-30T09:41:19Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="2nd reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4075</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4075</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (under the Ten Minute Rule)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Flooding Bill</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the responsibilities and duties of certain authorities and agencies in respect of inland flood prevention; to make provision about the powers of local flood authorities and Internal Drainage Boards; to require the Secretary of State to report to Parliament on the funding of local flood authorities and Internal Drainage Boards; to provide for the designation of Internal Drainage Board pumps as critical national infrastructure; to require the Secretary of State to prepare and publish a report on the potential merits of establishing a Flood Compensation Fund to support homeowners whose primary residence has become unsaleable as a direct result of flooding; to make provision about flood reinsurance schemes; to make provision about the responsibilities of developers and water companies in respect of the provision of drainage for new housing developments; to make water companies statutory consultees for certain planning applications; to place a duty on fire and rescue services to respond to flood events; to make provision about national and local digital mapping of flood incidence and risk; and for connected purposes;
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T14:33:53Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4012</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4012</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Sentencing Act 2026</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision about the sentencing, release and management after sentencing of offenders; to make provision about bail; to make provision about the removal from the United Kingdom of foreign criminals; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T14:15:58Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Consideration of Commons amendments and / or reasons">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4004</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4004</link>
<category>Government Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Diego Garcia Military Base and British Indian Ocean Territory Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to give effect to, and make provision in connection with, an agreement between the governments of the United Kingdom and the Republic of Mauritius concerning the Chagos Archipelago.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T13:51:46Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="Royal Assent">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3421</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/3421</link>
<category>Hybrid Bill</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>Holocaust Memorial Act 2026</title>
<description>
A Bill to make provision for expenditure by the Secretary of State and the removal of restrictions in respect of certain land for or in connection with the construction of a Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T13:34:26Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="1st reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4074</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4074</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Armed Forces Compensation Scheme and War Pension Scheme (Report) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to require the Secretary of State to report to Parliament on the potential merits of disregarding compensation received under the War Pension Scheme and Armed Forces Compensation Scheme for the purpose of calculating entitlement to Pension Credit and to other means-tested benefits for which such payments are not disregarded in full; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T12:26:06Z</a10:updated>
</item>
<item p4:stage="1st reading">
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4073</guid>
<link>https://bills.parliament.uk/bills/4073</link>
<category>Private Members' Bill (Presentation Bill)</category>
<category>Commons</category>
<title>
Local Government Reorganisation (Requirement for Referendum) Bill
</title>
<description>
A Bill to provide that any reorganisation of local government in England involving changes to electoral boundaries, the establishment of combined authorities, or other specified changes may not be undertaken unless such reorganisation has been approved by a simple majority of residents of any affected local government area voting in a referendum; to make provision about the organisation of such referendums; and for connected purposes.
</description>
<a10:updated>2026-01-29T12:24:17Z</a10:updated>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>